https://www.adopthelp.com/contact-us/

Skip to primary navigation Skip to main content Skip to footerConfidential 24 Hours 800-637-7999
We’re excited to speak with you!
Contact us to receive more information
Call us at 800-637-7999 for immediate assistance or to speak with an adoption specialist.
Fill out the form below and we will send you information about our program.
City
StateAlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyomingArmed Forces AmericasArmed Forces EuropeArmed Forces Pacific
State
ZIP Code
I am*Prospective Adoptive ParentPregnant Considering AdoptionI amChoose OneProspective Adoptive ParentPregnant - Considering Placing My ChildWhen is your estimated due date?Please Choose OneWithin the next 3 monthsWithin the next 6 monthsChild Already BornI Don't Know YetMessageEmailThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
Inside you will receive:
How our program worksBenefits of Private Placement AdoptionContact information for your personal adoption specialist
All Communications Are Confidential
AdoptHelp Website Disclaimer Statement Acceptance by AdoptHelp, Inc. and/or AdoptHelp Law Center (“AdoptHelp”) of e-mail through this website shall not constitute acceptance of an engagement to provide legal services nor shall it establish an attorney-client relationship. Without a written agreement or engagement letter, AdoptHelp shall not treat as confidential any information provided by e-mail. Terms and Conditions of Use The materials located at www.adopthelp.com (the “Website”) are provided by AdoptHelp for information purposes only and shall not constitute legal advice. The use of the Website by the user or browser (“You”) is subject to the following terms and conditions:
NO ATTORNEY – CLIENT RELATIONSHIP / INFORMATIONAL PURPOSE ONLY
The materials available on this Website have been prepared by AdoptHelp and are intended for informational purposes ONLY. The information provided on this Website is provided only as general information, which may or may not reflect the most current legal developments. The opinions expressed at or through this Website are the opinions of the individual author and may not reflect the opinions of AdoptHelp or any individual attorney or case worker.
USE IN OTHER JURISDICTIONS
The attorneys of AdoptHelp practice law only in jurisdictions in which AdoptHelp and its attorneys are properly authorized to do so. AdoptHelp does not seek to represent anyone in any jurisdiction where this Website does not comply or is in any way inconsistent with the rules governing communication of legal services in a particular state.
NO WARRANTIES/LIMITATION OF LIABILITY. INFORMATION PROVIDED ON THIS WEBSITE IS PROVIDED ON AN “AS IS” BASIS WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR NON-INFRINGEMENT. ADOPTHELP PERIODICALLY ADDS, CHANGES, IMPROVES OR UPDATES THE INFORMATION ON THIS WEBSITE WITHOUT NOTICE. ADOPTHELP ASSUMES NO LIABILITY OR RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY ERRORS OR OMISSIONS IN THE CONTENT OF THIS WEBSITE.
THIRD PARTY LINKS. AdoptHelp has included some links to related internet sites maintained by third parties. Neither AdoptHelp nor its affiliates operate or control, in any respect, any information, products or services on such linked sites. In addition, AdoptHelp does not guarantee the timeliness, sequence, accuracy, completeness, reliability or content of such information.
Any testimonials or endorsements found on this website do not constitute a guarantee, warranty, or prediction regarding the outcome of your legal matter.
PRIVACY STATEMENT
You should NOT send confidential information or information that you regard as privileged to AdoptHelp until you have received written acceptance from AdoptHelp of any legal services you may request. The content of any correspondence you send via the Internet or e-mail will not be considered confidential unless you have received such written confirmation.
GENERAL INFORMATION
AdoptHelp reserves the right to change these terms at any time, effective immediately upon posting on the Website. Please check this page of the Website periodically. If you violate these terms of use, AdoptHelp may terminate your use of the Website, bar you from future use of AdoptHelp and/or take appropriate legal action against you.
USE OF THE WEBSITE. AdoptHelp authorizes you to view, copy, download and print the documents on this Website, subject to the following conditions: (1) The documents may be used solely for personal, noncommercial, and informational purposes; (2) The documents may NOT be modified; and (3) The following copyright notice and permission notice must appear on each document: “2004 AdoptHelp. All Rights Reserved.”
PRIVACY POLICY
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for AdoptHelp. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any unnecessary third party.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website.
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 800-637-7999.
Should you have any questions about these terms and conditions, please contact contactus@adopthelp.com.
Pregnant?
